[
  {
    "front": "est",
    "back": "東"
  },
  {
    "front": "ouest",
    "back": "西"
  },
  {
    "front": "sud",
    "back": "南"
  },
  {
    "front": "nord",
    "back": "北"
  },
  {
    "front": "air, ciel",
    "back": "空"
  },
  {
    "front": "vent",
    "back": "風"
  },
  {
    "front": "matin",
    "back": "朝"
  },
  {
    "front": "nuit",
    "back": "夜"
  },
  {
    "front": "soir, crépuscule",
    "back": "夕"
  },
  {
    "front": "direction, côté, méthode, carré",
    "back": "方"
  }
]
